filip stojanovski

graphic designer // brand identity // ui&ux

about

nationality -- macedonian born in -- kumanovo date -- 26/10/1992 currently living in -- kumanovo

contact

mail -- shtergu1@gmail.com phone -- +389 78 655 463

links

behance.net/shtergu

profile

I'm Filip, a 29 years old designer from Macedonia, Kumanovo with vast experience in brand identity design and strategy, UI/UX design and marketing strategy. You have a problem? Bring it up, let's work our way to the solution. You can't pin-point the problem? I'll do my very best and try to solve it.

I'm a natural problem solver, an objective and logical thinker and very much detail oriented. In my 9 years of experience in the design industry, I've worked with Red Bull on their marketing, 420 Hemp Fest on their re-brand and marketing strategy, AutoScout24 on their digital marketing, to name a few. Avid fan of nature, photography and I love my dog til death do us apart.

education

instituto tecnico statale industriale

2008 - 2011 // Brescia, Italy

computer science and automation

ugd goce delcev

2012 - 2016 // Stip, Macedonia

Italian language and literature

work experience

short summary; started in 2012 as a freelance logo designer, self-taught.

freelance

2012 - present

freelance designer on Upwork.

shtergu

2017 - 2020

owner and art director in design agency specialized in brand identity design, strategy and marketing.

manypixels

2020 - 2021

senior graphic designer, multidisciplinary.

flote

2021 - 2021

brand manager and marketing officer

objective

my objective, professionally, is to always bring a solution to a problem that's most pragmatic and easy to implement, rather than being pretty and completely useless.

languages

english			
italian			
spanish			
macedonian			

skills

nhatashan

priotosriop			
illustrator			
indesign			
figma			
xd			
video edt			



portfolio of works - logo designs



















portfolio of works - posters and social media











